# Darwin Ameli

## Technician ES in Computer Science

Bellevaux 7
2000 Neuchâtel
Switzerland
06/01/2000
+41 78 913 xx xx
didi.ameli@gmail.com
linkedin.com/in/darwin-ameli
github.com/didix13

#### **SUMMARY**

With 8 years of studies in computer science, I have acquired a lot of theoretical knowledge in the field. I spent half of my apprenticeship in a company on a part-time basis to learn and familiarize myself with company life. This allowed me to learn how to manage customers, organize my work as well as how to deal with stress in the face of challenges.

Through my group and personal works, I developed the ability to work in teams and collaborate to achieve our goals.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Swiss military service** — *Pioneer*

June - October 2020

Establishment of the integrated military telecommunications network.

## **UNINE**, Neuchâtel — IT Apprentice

2018 - 2020

University of Neuchâtel

Back-end and Front-end department, maintenance of the IT infrastructure and assistance to students and collaborators.

## **STEG Electronics AG**, Marin — *IT Apprentice*

2015 - 2018

IT and electronics solution store

After Sales Services, Help-Desk, Seller.

#### **FORMATION**

## **HEG Arc**, Neuchâtel — Bsc in Business Information Technology

2023 - now

Bachelor degree HES

The University of Applied Sciences (HEG Arc) is one of the domains of

#### **INTERESTS**

Cyber Security

Cloud-based technologies

Innovation

AI (Machine / Deep Learning)

DevOps

#### **HOBBIES**

President - Neuchâtel Chess club - Captain of 3rd league

Model - Freelance model

CTF Player - World Hacking Competition in teams (OpenToAll / OpenBlue / Weak But Leet)

#### **LANGUAGES**

French: C2 English: C1 German: A2 Italian: A2

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### **Tools**

Terraform, Ansible, LXD, HAProxy, Traefik, Portainer, Docker, Kubernetes, MS Office, MS Visual Studio IDE, PyCharm, PhpStorm, NetBeans, Git, Nano, Vim, PowerShell ISE, XAMPP, .NET MAUI the Haute Ecole Arc.

Globalmark: 5.3 / 6

## **CPNE**, Neuchâtel — Computer Science Technician

2021 - 2023

Tertiary degree ES

Centre de formation professionnelle neuchâtelois

Globalmark: 4.95 / 6

## **CPLN**, Neuchâtel — CFC Computer scientist

2015 - 2021

Secondary level 2

Centre Professionnel du Littoral Neuchâtelois

Globalmark: 5.2 / 6

## Centre du Mail, Neuchâtel — Secondary School

2011 - 2015

**Elementary Secondary School** 

#### **WORKS**

### athenais.tech — Website

Automated Optical Inspection with deep learning, website to showcase the solutions and systems that athenais provides.

## **didix13.com** — Personal website

Apache web server, handmade to play with bare metal servers and services (to test new IaC tools)

## Acier D'ici — Panatere SA Project

Projet d'innovation dans la communication de recyclage d'acier en circuit court dans la Watch Valley

## **BrainIF** — Neurotechnology Project

Side project about implementing micro-electrodes on the brain to create interfaces, solving brain diseases and more.

## **FreeWater** — Self-sufficient Fountain

FreeWater was a school project with three co-workers, the goal was to create a fountain that could take the moisture out of the air and convert it into drinking water.

#### Monitoring

Prometheus, Grafana, Loki

#### Database

Oracle, PostgreSQL, MS Access, MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB, MariaDB

## Languages

Java, C#, Python, Bash, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL, PowerShell, x86 Assembly

#### Cloud

AWS,Docker Hub, MS Azure, Google Cloud Platform

## **Operating Systems**

Windows 11+, Windows Server 2022, MacOS Sonoma, Ubuntu, Kali Linux, Arch Linux

#### **HONOURS & REWARDS**

## Model

Mister Fête des Vendanges Neuchâtel 2023 - Winner Embassy of Peru Fashion Show - Model La Maladière Mall Fashion Show - Model

CTF (source ctftime.org)
2022 41th out of 35'875 teams
2021 1st out of 36'812 teams
2020 3rd out of 35'954 teams
2019 16th out of 24'815 teams
2018 35th out of 17'956 teams
2017 6'229 out of 14'985 teams

## **Bounty**

2019 La Poste, E-voting Intrusion Test - 400 CHF